const cards =  [
  {
    id: 1,
    level: "medium",
    question: "What's the capital city of Hungary?",
    answer: "The capital city of Hungary is Budapest.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1616432902940-b7a1acbc60b3?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    level: "hard",
    question: "What's the capital city of Uzbekistan?",
    answer: "The capital city of Uzbekistan is Tashkent.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1623064696935-0898cae58292?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1074&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    level: "medium",
    question: "What's the capital city of the Czech Republic?",
    answer: "The capital city of the Czech Republic is Prague.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1564511287568-54483b52a35e?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    level: "easy",
    question: "What's the capital city of South Korea?",
    answer: "The capital city of Korea is Seoul",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1506816561089-5cc37b3aa9b0?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1575&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    level: "medium",
    question: "What's the capital city of Australia?",
    answer: "The capital city of Australia is Canberra.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1545225383-f5596b804c22?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1176&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    level: "medium",
    question: "What's the capital city of Croatia?",
    answer: "The capital city of Croatia is Zagreb.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1582456032629-4a54a1a65697?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1832&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    level: "easy",
    question: "What's the capital city of Poland?",
    answer: "The capital city of Poland is Warsaw.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1607427293702-036933bbf746?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1932&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    level: "hard",
    question: "What's the capital city of Kyrgyzstan?",
    answer: "The capital city of Kyrgyzstan is Bishkek.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1629340209850-91da481357bf?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1074&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    level: "easy",
    question: "What's the capital city of Portugal?",
    answer: "The capital city of Portugal is Lisbon.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1501927023255-9063be98970c?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1074&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    level: "medium",
    question: "What's the capital city of Belgium?",
    answer: "The capital city of Belgium is Brussels.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1677234576844-12c1cbd09658?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1171&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    level: "easy",
    question: "What's the capital city of France?",
    answer: "The capital city of France is Paris.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1502602898657-3e91760cbb34?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1173&q=80"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    level: "easy",
    question: "What's the capital city of Indonesia?",
    answer: "The capital city of France is Jakarta.",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1555899434-94d1368aa7af?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80"
  },
]


export default cards;